You're insecure
Don't know what for.
You're turning heads when you walk
through the do-o-or
Don't need make up
To cover up
Being the way that you are
is enou-o-ough
Everyone else in the room can see it
Everyone else but you...
Baby, you light up my world
like nobody else
The way that you flip your hair
gets me overwhelmed
But when you smile at the ground
It ain't hard to tell
You don't know
Oh, Oh
You don't know you're beautiful
If only you saw
what I can see
You'll understand why
I want you so desperately.
Right now I'm looking at you
And I can't believe
You don't know
Oh, oh,
You don't know you're beautiful
Oh,oh,
That what makes you beautiful
So c-come on.
You got it wrong.
To prove I'm right
I put it in a song.
I don't know why
You're being shy,
And turn away when I look
into your eye-eye-eyes,
Everyone else in the room can see it.
Everyone else but you.
Baby, you light up my world like nobody else,
The way that you flip your hair
gets me overwhelmed
But when you smile at the ground
It ain't hard to tell
You don't know
Oh, oh,
You don't know you're beautiful,
If only you saw
what I can see
You'll understand why
I want you so desperately,
Right now I'm looking at you
and I can't believe,
You don't know,
Oh, oh,
You don't know you're beautiful
Oh oh,
That what makes you beautiful.
Baby, you light up my world
like nobody else
The way that you flip your hair
gets me overwhelmed
But when you smile at the ground
It ain't hard to tell.
You don't know
Oh, oh,
You don't know you're beautiful
Baby, you light up my world
like nobody else
The way that you flip your hair
gets me overwhelmed
But when you smile at the ground
It ain't hard to tell.
You don't know
Oh, oh,
You don't know you're beautiful
If only you saw
what I can see
You'll understand why
I want you so desperately.
Right now I'm looking at you
And I can't believe
You don't know,
Oh, oh,
You don't know you're beautiful
Oh oh,
Thats what makes you beautiful.
Subtitles by Aurobindo Debnath